<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Shahar Avigezer</title>
    <link>https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Shahar Avigezer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3 New Tools I Picked Up and What I Like Most About Them</title>
      <link>https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/new-dev-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/new-dev-tools/</guid>
      <description>As a strong believer in the idea that a new job means new habits, I&amp;rsquo;m always looking for ways to improve my workflow and boost productivity. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing 3 new tools that I&amp;rsquo;ve started using and highlighting the features that I like most. So, if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for some new tools to add to your developer toolkit, read on!
Wrap Wrap a next-level terminal, developed in Rust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bouncing Back from Layoff: How I Coped and Found a New Way Forward</title>
      <link>https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/bounce-back-from-layoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/bounce-back-from-layoffs/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Losing your job can be a tough time, and it&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon to feel lonely and uncertain. In this blog post, I share my own experience of being laid off and how I coped with it. I&amp;rsquo;ll add some tips that can help with the emotional and practical aspects of job loss. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re currently going through a layoff or just want to be prepared for the future, this post is for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rich Content</title>
      <link>https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo ships with several &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugos-built-in-shortcodes&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;
 for rich content, along with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Privacy Config&lt;/a&gt;
 and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Takeaways From My First Job as a Software Developer</title>
      <link>https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/first-year-takeaways/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shahar-avigezer.github.io/blog/first-year-takeaways/</guid>
      <description>1 - Reading and understanding others’ code is one of the most valuable skills you can develop. 90% of my first challenges were integrating into an existing code base so most of my day included reading and debugging to figure out how things work. I dedicated time to learn and unravel the relevant code base in order to spot the exact place to seamlessly blend in and add my own code or refactor existing code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
